FBX file format
Now, when using the FBX file format,
add or remove multiple virtual models at the same time.
Through this function,
you can add other objects or virtual models
when you keep the object in the current scene.
Go to the menu,
File, Add or Add,
select the FBX format,
select the file you need to import,
and select Open.
In the FBX dialogue box,
change the load type to Add.
You can choose Avatar or Trim as the target type.
Now, when you import or add FBX files,
it will have the same settings as importing OPJ files.
Select a copy,
then click on the water glue tool on the top right of the location ball
and stick it on the costume.
Repeat the process,
import and copy multiple FBX files
and continue other operations.
Using the FBX file format,
import or remove multiple virtual models
will help you better complete the multi-role scene production,
instead of only using the content of one role.
Select the FBX file you want to import.
In the FBX dialogue box,
set the load type to Add,
and the target type to virtual model.
For the human-type virtual model,
click on Automated Automated Portrait,
and it will automatically create a portrait in the import process.
In the object bar,
you can choose the relevant content of the import file,
such as joint animation.
Now you can set the axis rotation
or enter the moving value
to adjust the virtual model to the right position.
Here I will set the moving value of the two-meter Z axis.
When you enter the moving value,
when an object is placed below the ground,
you can click to align the ground.
They will automatically be placed above the ground after being imported.
Click to move the costume to the starting point of the action.
The costume will automatically move to the virtual model near the starting point.
Click to confirm and click to import the file.
Open the animation editor.
Let's preview the animation.
You can import the costume corresponding to the second virtual model,
set the same moving value,
and let them match.
Open the simulation,
wear the costume,
and start recording the animation.
When exporting FBX files,
you can also export all virtual models,
or select an independent virtual model to export.